// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " If the number 467X4 is divisible by 9, find the value of the digit marked as X.",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "7"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " Find the HCF of 210, 385, and 735?",
    answer: "35",
    options: [
      "7",
      "14",
      "21",
      "35"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " Find the largest 4 digit number that is exactly divisible by 66?",
    answer: "9966",
    options: [
      "9987",
      "9916",
      "9912",
      "9966"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the area of a triangle with base 5 meters and height 10 meters?",
    answer: "25 square meters",
    options: [
      "20 square meters",
      "25 square meters",
      "35 square meters",
      "40 square meters"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " Find the missing term of the given expression: 18.834 + 818.34 -? = 618.43?",
    answer: "218.744",
    options: [
      "218.744",
      "217.644",
      "217.844",
      "217.744"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " Vikas and Mohan working together can complete a work in 6 days. If Vikas alone completes the same work in 10 days, in how many days Mohan alone can complete the same work?",
    answer: "15 days",
    options: [
      "13 days",
      "14 days",
      "16 days",
      "15 days"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " If January 1, 1996, was Monday, what day of the week was January 1, 1997?",
    answer: "Wednesday",
    options: [
      "Thursday",
      "Wednesday",
      "Friday",
      "Sunday"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " How many times the hands of a clock coincide in a day?",
    answer: "22",
    options: [
      "17",
      "21",
      "22",
      "24"
    ]
  },

{
    numb: 9,
    question: " 40 % of 280 = ?",
    answer: "112",
    options: [
      "112",
      "116",
      "115",
      "120"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "If a - b = 3 and a2 + b2 = 29, find the value of ab." ,
    answer: "10",
    options: [
      "10",
      "12",
      "15",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "RQP, ONM, _, IHG, FED, find the missing letters?" ,
    answer: "LKJ",
    options: [
      "CDE",
      "LKI",
      "LKJ",
      "BAC"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "PETAL: FLOWER" ,
    answer: "Engine: Car",
    options: [
      "Pen: Paper",
      "Ball: Game",
      "Cat: Dog",
      "Engine: Car"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: " Pointing to a photograph, a man said, I have no brother, and that man's father is my father's son. Whose photograph was it?" ,
    answer: "His son",
    options: [
      "His own",
      "His son",
      "His father",
      "His nephew"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "If in a certain language, NOIDA is coded as OPJEB, how is DELHI coded in that language?" ,
    answer: "EFMIJ",
    options: [
      "CDKGH",
      "IHLED",
      "EFMIJ",
      "FGNJK"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: " Peter is in the East of Tom and Tom is in the North of John. Mike is in the South of John then in which direction of Peter is Mike?" ,
    answer: "South-West",
    options: [
      "South-West",
      "South-East",
      "South",
      "North-East"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Choose one of the following options that means the opposite of the given word; Luminous: " ,
    answer: "Dim",
    options: [
      "Bright",
      "soft",
      "clear",
      "Dim"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "A person who travels on foot. ",
    answer: "pedestrian",
    options: [
      "pedestrian",
      "traveler",
      "walker",
      "health conscious"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: ".............Himalayas provides protection to India against enemies. " ,
    answer: "The",
    options: [
      "No Articles",
      "An",
      "The",
      "A"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question:"They walked ....... the edge of the land.",
    answer: "Either A or B",
    options: [
      "up to",
      "until",
      "Either A or B",
      "there"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Tick the correct synonym of the given word: Brief" ,
    answer: "Short",
    options: [
      "Partial",
      "Short",
      "Limited",
      "Little"
    ]
  },
];